Walter B. Cannon Papers 1905-1928 Mss.B.C163.1
American Philosophical Society
- Walter B. Cannon Papers, 1905-1928 (Box 1-6)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1914 Apr 2; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 2)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1914 May 20; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 2)
  - to William W. Keen, 1914 May 21; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 2)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1914 May 23; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 2)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1914 May 22; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 2)
  - to William W. Keen, 1914 May 25; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 2)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1914 May 28; 3p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 2)
  - to William W. Keen, 1914 June 1; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 2)
  - to William W. Keen, 1914 June 6; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 2)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1914 June 8; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 2)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1914 June 9; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 2)
  - to William W. Keen, 1914 June 11; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 2)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1914 July 16; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 2)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1914 Aug 10; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 2)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1914 Aug 15; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 2)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1914 Aug 20; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 2)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1914 Aug 31; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 2)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1914 Sep 3; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 2)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1914 Sep 4; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 2)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1914 Sep 5; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 2)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1914 Sep 16; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 2)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1914 Sept 18; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 2)
  - to William W. Keen, 1914 Sep 23; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 2)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1914 Sep 23; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 2)
  - to William W. Keen, 1914 Sep 25; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 2)
  - to William W. Keen, 1914 Nov 2; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 2)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1914 Nov 3; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 2)
  - to William W. Keen, 1914 Nov 5; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 2)
  - to William W. Keen, 1914 Nov 20; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 2)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1915 Jan 8; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 2)
  - to William W. Keen, 1915; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 2)
  - to William W. Keen, 1915 Jan 9; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 2)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1915 Jan 11; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 2)
  - to William W. Keen, 1915 Jan 20; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 2)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1915 Jan 25; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 2)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1915 Jan 26; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 2)
  - to William W. Keen, 1915 Jan 27; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 2)
  - to William W. Keen, 1915 Mar 5; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1915 Mar 6; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1915 Mar 10; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to William W. Keen, 1915 Mar 16; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to William W. Keen, 1915 Mar 22; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1915 Mar 26; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to William W. Keen, 1915 Mar 27; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1915 Mar 29; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to William W. Keen, 1915 Mar 31; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1915 Apr 1; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to William W. Keen, 1915 Apr 5; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1915 Apr 7; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1915 Apr 14; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to William W. Keen, 1915 Apr 15; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1915 Apr 16; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1915 Apr 19; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to William W. Keen, 1915 Apr 24; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1915 May 5; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to William W. Keen, 1915 May 6; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1915 May 13; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to William W. Keen, 1915 May 15; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to H.R. Hadwen, 1915 May 17; 5p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Dr. Vaughan, 1915 May 17; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1915 May 17; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to William W. Keen, 1915 May 19; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1915 May 19; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to William W. Keen, 1915 May 20; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1915 May 20; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1915 May 21; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to William W. Keen, 1915 May 21; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1915 May 24; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to William W. Keen, 1915 June 9; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to William W. Keen, 1915 June 10; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1915 July 4; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Editors of Zoophily, 1916 July 11; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1916 July 12; 1p.; Logan, R. R. (Box 3)
  - to R. R. Logan, 1916 July 14; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1916 July 18; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1916 July 18; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to William W. Keen, 1916 July 26; 3p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1916 July 28; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1916 July 30; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1916 Aug 6; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1916 Sep 28; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to William W. Keen, 1916 Sep 29; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1916 Pct 3; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to William W. Keen, 1916 Oct 4; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to William W. Keen, 1917 Feb 10; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1917 Mar 27; 1p.; Lyon, E. P. (Box 3)
  - to E. P. Lyon, 1917 Apr 3; 5p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
    Includes Cannon to Lyon, April 2, 1917.
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1917 Apr 21; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to William W. Keen, 1917 Apr 23; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Harvey Cushing, 1917 Apr 29; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1917 Nov 23; 1p.; Lambert, Alexander (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1918 Dec 6; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1918 Dec 23; 3p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Jan 7; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Jan 7; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Jan 15; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to William W. Keen, 1919 Feb 1; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Feb 4; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Red Cross, 1919 Feb 4; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to William W. Keen, 1919 Feb 5; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Feb 5; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to S. J. Meltzer, 1919 Feb 5; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to William W. Keen, 1919 Feb 6; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Feb 7; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Feb 7; 2p.; Meltzer, S. J. (Box 3)
  - to S. J. Meltzer, 1919 Feb 11; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to J. J. R. MacLeod, 1919 Feb 13; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Feb 14; 1p.; Howell, W. H. (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Feb 16; 1p.; Lambert, Alexander (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Feb 17; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Feb 18; 2p.; MacLeod, J. J. R. (Box 3)
  - to J. J. R. MacLeod, 1919 Feb 21; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Feb 21; 1p.; Howell, W. H. (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Feb 25; 1p.; Lambert, Alexander (Box 3)
  - to Alexander Lambert, 1919 Mar 4; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Mar 8; 1p.; Meltzer, S. J. (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Mar 13; 1p.; Lambert, Alexander (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Mar 16; 1p.; Lambert, Alexander (Box 3)
  - to William W. Keen, 1919 Mar 17; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Mar 19; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Alexander Lambert, 1919 Mar 20; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Mar 20; 1p.; Lambert, Alexander (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Mar 21; 1p.; Lambert, Alexander (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Mar 21; 1p.; Mendel, Lafayette B., (Lafayette Benedict), 1872-1935 (Box 3)
  - to Alexander Lambert, 1919 Mar 22; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to J. J. R. MacLeod, 1919 Mar 22; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Mar 26; 2p.; MacLeod, J. J. R. (Box 3)
  - to J. J. R. MacLeod, 1919 Mar 28; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Alexander Lambert, 1919 Mar 28; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Mar 29; 2p.; Hussey, R. G. (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 May 4; 2p.; Hoell, W. H. (Box 3)
  - to Authors of Kenn's Surgery, vol. VII, 1919 May 13; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 June 10; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 June 21; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 June 21; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 July 12; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to William W. Keen, 1919 July 14; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 July 16; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 July 25; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 July 29; 3p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Authors of Kenn's Surgery, vol. VII, 1919 July 30; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 3)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Aug 5; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Aug 8; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Aug 11; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to Authors of Kenn's Surgery, vol. VII, 1919 Sep 5; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Sep 12; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Sep 22; 3p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Sep 23; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1919 Sep 26; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Sep 26; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Sep 27; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1919 Sep 30; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Oct 1; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1919 Oct 2; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Oct 2; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Oct 4; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Oct 11; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1919 Nov 3; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Nov 4; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1919 Nov 17; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Nov 19; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Nov 25; 1p.; Saunders, W. B. (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1919 Dec 1; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Dec 3; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1919 Dec 5; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Frank B. Kellogg, 1919 Dec 8; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1919 Dec 10; 1p.; Kellogg, Frank B. (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Jan 11; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Jan 14; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Jan 16; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Jan 17; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Jan 19; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Jan 20; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Jan 22; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Jan 24; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Jan 20; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Feb 3; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Feb 7; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Feb 24; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Mar 22; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Mar 24; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Apr 2; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Apr 2; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Apr 6; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Apr 7; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Apr 9; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Apr 14; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Apr 16; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 May 8; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 May 10; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 May 11; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 May 12; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 May 13; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 May 14; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 May 17; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 May 24; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 May 26; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 May 28; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 June 1; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 June 2; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 June 2; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 June 4; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 June 5; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 June 7; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 June 15; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Oct 6; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Oct 7; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Oct 8; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Oct 9; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Oct 11; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Oct 13; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Oct 14; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Oct 16; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Oct 20; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Oct 21; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Oct 24; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Oct 25; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Oct 26; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Oct 28; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Nov 1; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Nov 2; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Nov 4; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Nov 5; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Nov 6; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Nov 8; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Nov 9; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Nov 13; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to Simon Flexner, 1920 Nov 13; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Nov 15; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Nov 16; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Nov 16; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Nov 17; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Nov 17; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Nov 18; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Nov 18; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Nov 20; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Nov 20; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Nov 27; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Nov 29; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Dec 1; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Dec 2; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Dec 3; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Dec 4; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Dec 6; 2p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Dec 7; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to K. K. Koessler, 1920 Dec 8; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Dec 9; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Dec 16; 2p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)
  - to William W. Keen, 1920 Dec 17; 1p.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945 (Box 4)
  - to Walter B. Cannon, 1920 Dec 18; 1p.; Keen, William W., (William Williams), b. 1837 (Box 4)